{
    "id": "041dc62e3d354ff3ad6dd8a89873833a",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs: Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f9964830a74c4d6e900c0bc83c4da885",
            "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He is afraid to speak, lest he ………………………. be laughed at.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "can",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He said he ………………………….  not come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "shall"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Had I seen you, I ………………………. have come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "will",
                        "may"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ……………………… swim across the river when he was young.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "may"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He told me that he ………………………. not help me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "may",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………….. you live long!",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "May",
                        "Will",
                        "Shall"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I had studied medicine I ………………………. have become a doctor.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "will",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………….. have arrived in time, if I had not lost my way.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "could",
                        "can",
                        "will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………… very much like to see my old classmates.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ………………………. not hurry, we have  got plenty of time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "need",
                        "would",
                        "shall"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}